{
    "inputTimeWaitSecs": 360,
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "\\(3.52\\) &times; \\(7\\)",
        "answer": "24.64",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(68.7\\) &times; \\(0.944\\)",
        "answer": "64.8528",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(3\\) &div; \\(0\\) to 1 decimal place",
        "answer": "undefined",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(5.42\\) &times; \\(8.61\\)",
        "answer": "46.6662",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(1.5\\) &div; \\(-0.005\\) to 3 decimal places",
        "answer": "-300.000",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(540\\) &times; \\(-7.49\\)",
        "answer": "-4044.6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(6\\) &div; \\(1.3\\) to 0 decimal places",
        "answer": "5.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          0
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0.01\\) &div; \\(1\\) to 2 decimal places",
        "answer": "0.01",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(-0.009\\) &div; \\(0.2\\) to 0 decimal places",
        "answer": "-0.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          0
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(10.9\\) &times; \\(42\\)",
        "answer": "457.8",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0.013\\) &div; \\(0.05\\) to 3 decimal places",
        "answer": "0.260",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          3
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(685\\) &times; \\(0.551\\)",
        "answer": "377.435",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(-9.16\\) &times; \\(120\\)",
        "answer": "-1099.2",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(-0.613\\) &times; \\(9.05\\)",
        "answer": "-5.54765",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(66.5\\) &times; \\(0.431\\)",
        "answer": "28.6615",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0.05\\) &div; \\(0.001\\) to 0 decimal places",
        "answer": "50.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          0
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(-44.7\\) &times; \\(-1.59\\)",
        "answer": "71.073",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0.005\\) &div; \\(-6\\) to 4 decimal places",
        "answer": "-0.0008",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(3\\) &div; \\(1\\) to 1 decimal place",
        "answer": "3.0",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0.014\\) &div; \\(0.1\\) to 0 decimal places",
        "answer": "0.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          0
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(-0.15\\) &div; \\(1\\) to 4 decimal places",
        "answer": "-0.1500",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(0.849\\) &times; \\(-6.67\\)",
        "answer": "-5.66283",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(644\\) &times; \\(-0.379\\)",
        "answer": "-244.076",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0.1\\) &div; \\(-0.1\\) to 0 decimal places",
        "answer": "-1.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          0
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(-0.342\\) &times; \\(8.1\\)",
        "answer": "-2.7702",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(-1\\) &div; \\(0\\) to 0 decimal places",
        "answer": "undefined",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          0
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0.016\\) &div; \\(0.01\\) to 1 decimal place",
        "answer": "1.6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(-0.07\\) &div; \\(1\\) to 2 decimal places",
        "answer": "-0.07",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(-619\\) &times; \\(4.48\\)",
        "answer": "-2773.12",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(-441\\) &times; \\(348\\)",
        "answer": "-153468",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(9\\) &div; \\(-1.3\\) to 4 decimal places",
        "answer": "-6.9231",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(11\\) &div; \\(0.003\\) to 4 decimal places",
        "answer": "3666.6667",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(-0.01\\) &div; \\(0.005\\) to 1 decimal place",
        "answer": "-2.0",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0.06\\) &div; \\(0.08\\) to 4 decimal places",
        "answer": "0.7500",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          4
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(-1.1\\) &div; \\(-0.1\\) to 0 decimal places",
        "answer": "11.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          0
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(0.159\\) &times; \\(0.351\\)",
        "answer": "0.055809",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0.11\\) &div; \\(4\\) to 0 decimal places",
        "answer": "0.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          0
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(-7.48\\) &times; \\(0.859\\)",
        "answer": "-6.42532",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0.4\\) &div; \\(-0.05\\) to 1 decimal place",
        "answer": "-8.0",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          1
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(220\\) &times; \\(0.78\\)",
        "answer": "171.6",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(33.5\\) &times; \\(670\\)",
        "answer": "22445",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(0.283\\) &times; \\(-2.24\\)",
        "answer": "-0.63392",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0\\) &div; \\(0\\) to 0 decimal places",
        "answer": "undefined",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          0
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(6.4\\) &times; \\(0.886\\)",
        "answer": "5.6704",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(0.706\\) &times; \\(6.71\\)",
        "answer": "4.73726",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(823\\) &times; \\(4.73\\)",
        "answer": "3892.79",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(63.2\\) &times; \\(1.82\\)",
        "answer": "115.024",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0\\) &div; \\(0.08\\) to 0 decimal places",
        "answer": "0.",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          0
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Round the result of \\(0.004\\) &div; \\(-1\\) to 2 decimal places",
        "answer": "-0.00",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ],
        "expectedDps": [
          2
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "\\(136\\) &times; \\(533\\)",
        "answer": "72488",
        "numberInputTypes": [
          "dec"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }